## EUGEN CODA FRONTEND DEVELOPER



# PERSONAL PROFILE

Hard-working, self-taught frontend developer.

Seeking to further improve my software development skills by building modern and easy-to-use web applications.

Ability to work with teams and individuals with different backgrounds and experience levels.

People management experience of 4+ years, with a professional background in finance and accounting.

## SKILLS

React, Angular, Jutro (Guidewire)

Guidewire Policy Center

Guidewire Claim Center

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

Pug, Bootstrap & Material UI

Node.js (express.js)

MongoDB (mongoose)

Git, Bitbucket, GitHub

Jira. Confluence

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Frontend Developer**

FEB 2024 - CURRENT (WARSAW, POLAND)

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Developing an accounts payable application for a leading payment processing company using the Angular framework
- Working in an agile environment with daily stand-ups, keeping track of user stories/bugs in Jira, and actively participating in sprint planning and sprint retrospectives
- Collaborating with design, product, and backend teams
- Creating application functionality according to business requirements and connecting the frontend components to the data model provided by the backend applications
- Implementing UI/UX design into code, creating the visual elements of the application with the focus on responsiveness and accessibility

### **EY GDS, Frontend Developer**

MAY 2022 - JAN 2024 (WARSAW, POLAND)

- Developing Digital Guidewire applications using Jutro (React) framework
- Backend integration with Guidewire Policy Center and Claim Center

## EUGEN CODA FRONTEND DEVELOPER



## **EDUCATION**

University of Bucharest (Romania)
Bachelor in Economics, 2009

## LANGUAGES

Romanian: Native

English: Advanced

German: Advanced

Russian: Intermediate

Polish: Beginner

## CONTACT

Warsaw, Poland

Mail: coda.eugen@gmail.com

Website: <u>eugencoda.github.io</u>

GitHub: EugenCoda

LinkedIn: eugen-coda

Twitter: @coda eugen

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Sollers Consulting, Frontend Developer**

JUN 2021 - APR 2022 (WARSAW, POLAND)

 Developing Digital Guidewire applications using Jutro (React) framework

#### **Accenture, PTP Tower Lead**

JAN 2019 - DEC 2019 (WARSAW, POLAND)
JUL 2018 - DEC 2018 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)

## **Accenture, Service Delivery Team Lead**

JAN 2020 - OCT 2020 (WARSAW, POLAND)
JAN 2016 - JUN 2018 (BUCHAREST & IASI, ROMANIA)

### Accenture, Accounting Clerk

SEP 2015 - DEC 2015 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)

### **Wipro, Technical Support Associate**

OCT 2014 - AUG 2015 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)

### Strabag, Economist

APR 2012 - MAR 2014 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)

#### **Accenture, Accounting Clerk**

JAN 2010 - MAR 2009 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)

### **UPC Romania, Sales Agent**

FEB 2009 - SEP 2009 (BUCHAREST, ROMANIA)